University of Connecticut 1998.0186
Archives & Special Collections at the Thomas J. Dodd Research Center, University of Connecticut Libraries
- Series III: Wallace Moreland Files, 1964-1972
  - CNA - for Faculty - Alumni Center landscaping (Box 174:, Folder 2892)
  - Connecticut Farm Forum (Box 174:, Folder 2893)
  - Connecticut Industrial Development Commission (CDIC) (Box 174:, Folder 2894)
  - CONNPEP ( David Ivry, Director), 1968 October 28 (Box 174:, Folder 2895)
  - Connecticut Science Fair - Luncheon (Box 174:, Folder 2896)
  - Connecticut Chamber of Commerce (Box 174:, Folder 2897)
  - Connecticut State Grange (Box 174:, Folder 2898)
  - Connecticut Tree Protection Association, 1966 April 29 (Box 174:, Folder 2899)
  - Connecticut Valley Hospital Companion Program (Box 174:, Folder 2900)
  - Conservation and development of Eastern Connecticut (Box 174:, Folder 2901)
  - Conservation, Proposal TV Series on (Box 174:, Folder 2902)
  - Constitutional Convention (Box 174:, Folder 2903)
  - Continuing Education Services ( Robert B. Norris, Dean) (Box 174:, Folder 2904)
  - Constitutional Oaks (Box 174:, Folder 2905)
  - Cooperative Pharmacy (Box 174:, Folder 2906)
  - Corrections Department - University of Connecticut Programs (Box 175:, Folder 2907)
  - Council on Human Rights and Opportunities (Box 175:, Folder 2908)
  - Fairfield County magazine (Box 175:, Folder 2909)
  - Crowder, Dr. Louis (Box 175:, Folder 2910)
  - Crossgrove, Roger L. (Box 175:, Folder 2911)
  - CURE and CIP - News releases (Box 175:, Folder 2912)
  - Curcuru, Edmond H. (M.B.A. program, Stamford) (Box 175:, Folder 2913)
  - Cusick, Thomas J. (Division of Student Personnel) (Box 175:, Folder 2914)
  - D, 1964 (Box 175:, Folder 2915)
  - Daddario, Emilio Q. (U.S. representative) (Box 175:, Folder 2916)
  - Damman, Dr. A. W. H. (Box 175:, Folder 2917)
  - Danbury Exchange Club - Freedom Shrine, 1965 April (Box 175:, Folder 2918)
  - Deighton, Lee C. ( Encyclopedia of Education) (Box 175:, Folder 2919)
  - Dempsey, John N., Governor (Box 175:, Folder 2920)
  - Dean Hewes - Discipline, Students (Box 175:, Folder 2921)
  - Department of Community Affairs ( Nancy G. Becthel) (Box 175:, Folder 2922)
  - Department of Defense - Complaints re. cutback in Contracts (Box 175:, Folder 2923)
  - DOD. Critical of research policy (Box 175:, Folder 2924)
  - Development Administrators Training Program (Box 175:, Folder 2925)
  - Dodd, Thomas J. (U.S. Senator) (Box 175:, Folder 2926)
  - Dodd - Webb meeting, 1964 July 14 (Box 175:, Folder 2927)
  - Dormitories and Map - Alumni Quadrangle (Box 175:, Folder 2928)
  - Dozeman, Dr. Alvin (Box 175:, Folder 2929)
  - Draft statement (Box 175:, Folder 2930)
  - Drug Advisory Council Report (Box 175:, Folder 2931)
  - Drug Study Center - Proposed (Box 175:, Folder 2932)
  - Ducks (Box 175:, Folder 2933)
  - E (Box 175:, Folder 2934)
  - Earth Day (Box 175:, Folder 2935)
  - Eastern Education Network (Box 175:, Folder 2936)
  - Proposed Eastern Connecticut Recreation and Conservation Development Program, 1967-1968 (Box 175:, Folder 2937)
  - Eastern Education TV - Yale (Box 175:, Folder 2938)
  - Economic Opportunity, Act of 1964 (Box 175:, Folder 2939)
  - Education Report (Complaints requested) (Box 175:, Folder 2940)
  - Education, School of (Dr. William H. Roe, Dean) (Box 175:, Folder 2941)
  - EWA meeting, Washington, D.C. (Box 175:, Folder 2942)
  - Education Writers Association Tour (Box 175:, Folder 2943-2956)
  - Emergency Operations Techniques (Box 175:, Folder 2957)
  - Engineering, School of, 1963-1970 (Box 175:, Folder 2958)
  - Etherington, Edwin D. (Box 175:, Folder 2959)
  - Etherington Commission Report (Box 175:, Folder 2960)
  - Etherington Report (Box 175:, Folder 2961)
  - K - O Associates - Evaluation Committee (Box 175:, Folder 2962)
  - Evans, Dr. C. W. H. (Director, A-V Center) (Box 175:, Folder 2963)
  - Environmental Science Center (proposed) (Box 175:, Folder 2964)
  - Extension Study Committee, University (Box 175:, Folder 2965)
  - Exchange Program with Hampton Institute and University of Connecticut (Box 175:, Folder 2966)
  - Experimental College, 1969 (Box 175:, Folder 2967)
  - F (Box 176:, Folder 2968)
  - Faculty - Alumni Center (Box 176:, Folder 2969)
  - Faculty - Alumni Luncheon Expenses (Box 176:, Folder 2970)
  - Faculty - Yale Graduates (Box 176:, Folder 2971)
  - Farner, Frank (Intern) (Box 176:, Folder 2972)
  - Mansfield Amendment - Defense Appropriation Bill, 1968 (Box 176:, Folder 2973)
  - Senate Bill S3138, House Bill HR13881 - Animal Research, 1966 (Box 176:, Folder 2974)
  - HR 5710 Title IV, 1967 (Box 176:, Folder 2975)
  - Bill - HR 3141, 1966 (Box 176:, Folder 2976)
  - NDEA Fellowships (Box 176:, Folder 2977)
  - Title I of Higher Education Act, 1965 (Box 176:, Folder 2978)
  - Visit of Mark Feinberg to campus (Box 176:, Folder 2979)
  - Fellowship of Christian Athletes (Box 176:, Folder 2980)
  - Financial Aid Policy Committee, University Senate, University of Connecticut (Box 176:, Folder 2981-2982)
  - Fine Arts, School of ( Frank B. Cookson, Dean) (Box 176:, Folder 2983)
  - Project - Project (Dean Cookson) (Box 176:, Folder 2984)
  - Puppet Festival, 1970 Summer (Box 176:, Folder 2985)
  - Flying Feds (Box 176:, Folder 2986)
  - Flynn, Charles E. (Box 176:, Folder 2987)
  - Forestry - Letters regarding Extension's work in area (Box 176:, Folder 2988)
  - Foundations (Box 176:, Folder 2989)
  - Fraternity Study Report by Robert Carroll (Box 176:, Folder 2990)
  - President's Statement, Study Committee report (Box 176:, Folder 2991)
  - Fraternity Study Committee report (Final), 1964 October 19 (Box 176:, Folder 2992)
  - Sigma Chi Matter - Jerry Sullivan (Box 176:, Folder 2993)
  - Independent Tower President's Report, 1964 November (Box 176:, Folder 2994)
  - Phi Epsilon Pi - latest developments, 1965 January (Box 176:, Folder 2995)
  - Fraternity Study Committee material (from Pres. Babbidge) (Box 176:, Folder 2996)
  - Fraternity - Carroll Letter Study (Box 176:, Folder 2997)
  - Fraternity Study Committee minutes (Box 176:, Folder 2998)
  - Fraternity Study Committee meeting, 1964 July 19 (Box 176:, Folder 2999)
  - Free Press, UConn - Complaints (Box 176:, Folder 3000)
  - Friedman, Don, Review with, 1968 (Box 176:, Folder 3001)
  - G (Box 176:, Folder 3002)
  - Gant, Edward (Acting Provost), 1965-1966 (Box 176:, Folder 3003)
  - General Electric Interviews - News clips (Box 176:, Folder 3004)
  - Gerson, Louis (Box 176:, Folder 3005)
  - Gerontology, Institute of (Box 176:, Folder 3006)
  - Gift Brochure (Box 176:, Folder 3007)
  - Gill, Commissioner - Letters sent to (Box 176:, Folder 3008)
  - Ginsberg, Allen - re. LSD research (Box 176:, Folder 3009)
  - Glide-A-Ride (Box 176:, Folder 3010)
  - Glynn, John (Director, Labor Education Center) (Box 176:, Folder 3011)
  - Visit of Mr. Gold for luncheon (Box 176:, Folder 3012)
  - Goldmark, Dr. Peter (University of the Air) (Box 176:, Folder 3013)
  - Goodale, Larry - Complaint (Box 176:, Folder 3014)
  - Goodwin, Dorothy (Box 176:, Folder 3015)
  - Governor's Drug Program (Box 176:, Folder 3016)
  - Graduate School (Box 176:, Folder 3017-3019)
  - Greater Hartford Chamber of Commerce, Nucleus Committee (Box 176:, Folder 3020)
  - Greater Hartford Chamber of Commerce (Box 176:, Folder 3021)
  - Greer, Hugh, Memorial fund (Box 176:, Folder 3022)
  - Guidelines on Student Conduct, 1970 (Box 176:, Folder 3023)
  - Gulley Hall (Box 176:, Folder 3024)
  - H (Box 176:, Folder 3025)
  - Hancock, John, Awards for Excellence, 1963-1964 (Box 176:, Folder 3026)
  - Hansen, Henry (Co-op Extension) (Box 177:, Folder 3027)
  - Hartford Seminary - University of Connecticut affiliation (Box 177:, Folder 3028-3029)
  - Hartford Foundation for Public Giving (Box 177:, Folder 3030)
  - Hartford Insurance Group - Re. Channel 8 film (Box 177:, Folder 3031)
  - Hartford Tutorial (Box 177:, Folder 3032)
  - Hewes, Student Personnel, 1965-1966 (Box 177:, Folder 3033)
  - Hill, Evan G. (Head, Journalism Department) (Box 177:, Folder 3034)
  - Hodenfeld, G. K. Visit to campus (Box 177:, Folder 3035)
  - Home Economics, School of, 1967 (Box 177:, Folder 3036)
  - Homosexuals (Box 177:, Folder 3037)
  - Honors Program (Box 177:, Folder 3038)
  - Hook, Sidney (Box 177:, Folder 3039)
  - Horticulture Club (Box 177:, Folder 3040)
  - Hotel and Motel Interests, University of Connecticut (Box 177:, Folder 3041)
  - Houley, Robert D. - 35th District (Box 177:, Folder 3042)
  - Housing, Emergency, 1967 (Box 177:, Folder 3043)
  - Inner College (Box 177:, Folder 3044)
  - Institute of Materials Science (Box 177:, Folder 3045)
  - Institute: Pharmacy Research (Box 177:, Folder 3046)
  - Institute of International Studies (empty) (Box 177:, Folder 3047)
  - Material Sciences Building - Physics, Dedication, 1970-1971 (Box 177:, Folder 3048)
  - Public Service, Institute of (Box 177:, Folder 3049)
  - Institute of Water Resources (Box 177:, Folder 3050)
  - Internship (Congressional) (Box 177:, Folder 3051)
  - J (Box 177:, Folder 3052)
  - Jaycees, Connecticut, Young Farmer Program, 1970 February 6 (Box 177:, Folder 3053)
  - Jurev, Mrs. George, 1968 (Box 177:, Folder 3054)
  - K (Box 177:, Folder 3055)
  - Kappa Psi Meeting, 1964 (Box 177:, Folder 3056)
  - Karmel, Teresa A. (Box 177:, Folder 3057)
  - Kennedy, Joseph P., Jr., Foundation (Box 177:, Folder 3058)
  - Kilbourne, Orrine P. (Box 177:, Folder 3059)
  - Dr. Knobler - Student Teaching in North End of Hartford (Box 177:, Folder 3060)
  - L (Box 177:, Folder 3061)
  - Lamplighters, 1967-1968 (Box 177:, Folder 3062)
  - Lane Bryant Awards (Box 177:, Folder 3063)
  - Laurel Club Meeting re: Political Data Center (Box 177:, Folder 3064)
  - Law, School of (Box 177:, Folder 3065-3069)
  - Law Review Colloquium - Ed K. Ota, 1970 (Box 177:, Folder 3070)
  - Legislative modernization, Committee on - Meeting (Box 177:, Folder 3071)
  - Library ( John P. McDonnald) (Box 177:, Folder 3072)
  - League of Women Voters - Legislative Conference (Box 177:, Folder 3073)
  - Legislation - re. Disrupters (other universities), 1970 (Box 177:, Folder 3074)
  - Leonard, Douglas - New Jersey TV (Box 177:, Folder 3075)
  - Lindemann, Carl, VP NBC Sports (Box 177:, Folder 3076)
  - Liquor (Box 177:, Folder 3077)
  - Lockers - Norgaard (for faculty) (Box 177:, Folder 3078)
  - Lukens, John P. (Coordinator, State Commission on Youth Services) (Box 177:, Folder 3079)
  - Lupton, John ( Connecticut Republican Committee) (Box 177:, Folder 3080)
  - Lof, John C. (Director, University Computer Center) (Box 177:, Folder 3081)
  - Loy, Helen (Box 177:, Folder 3082)
  - Luckey, Eleaonore Braun (Box 177:, Folder 3083)
  - M (Box 177:, Folder 3084)
  - Maine, University of - Howard A. Keys (Box 177:, Folder 3085)
  - Maloney, Senator, papers (Box 177:, Folder 3086)
  - Management Council of Southeastern Connecticut (Box 177:, Folder 3086)
  - Mansfield Training School, 1968 (Box 177:, Folder 3087-3090)
  - Manter, Gerauld (photos, memorabilia), 1966 (Box 177:, Folder 3091-3092)
  - Marijuana and LSD (Box 177:, Folder 3093)
  - Marine Research Laboratory (Dr. John S. Rankin, Director) (Box 177:, Folder 3094)
  - Marland, Sidney, Nomination (Box 177:, Folder 3095)
  - Maryland, University of - Fixed graduated fee plan (Box 177:, Folder 3096)
  - UMass Fiscal Autonomy Legislation (Box 177:, Folder 3097)
  - Massachusetts Institute of Technology (Box 177:, Folder 3098)
  - MBA Program - Hartford (Box 177:, Folder 3099)
  - May, E. E. (Former Dean, School of Home Economics) (Box 177:, Folder 3100)
  - Mayfield, Marcia D. (UConn's first Presidential Scholar) (Box 177:, Folder 3101)
  - McDonald, John P. (Box 177:, Folder 3102)
  - McGuire, Morgan K. (Senator) - visit to campus, 1966 August 11 (Box 177:, Folder 3103)
  - McKain, Dr. Walter C. (Box 178:, Folder 3104)
  - McMahon, Brein, Lecture (by Senator William Fulbright) (Box 178:, Folder 3105)
  - Mental Health Center (Box 178:, Folder 3106)
  - Mental Health Center (Box 178:, Folder 3107)
  - Mental Health Task Force on Communications and Public (Box 178:, Folder 3108)
  - Michie, Alan A. (Box 178:, Folder 3109)
  - Monagan, John S. (US Representative, District Five) (Box 178:, Folder 3110)
  - Morriseau, James J. ( Educational Facilities Laboratories, Inc.) (Box 178:, Folder 3111)
  - Monnier, Dwight (Box 178:, Folder 3112)
  - Motor Pool - Accident with state car, 1968 May 8 (Box 178:, Folder 3113)
  - Murphy, Edith - Discussion with HDB (Box 178:, Folder 3114)
  - Museum, State (Proposed) (Box 178:, Folder 3115)
  - Museum of Art ( Myrvin S. Sadick, Director) (Box 178:, Folder 3116)
  - N (Box 178:, Folder 3117)
  - Narcotics (Box 178:, Folder 3118)
  - National Medal of Science (Box 178:, Folder 3119)
  - National Association of State Universities and Land-Grant Colleges (Box 178:, Folder 3120-3126)
  - Joint Office of Institutional Research ( Allan W. Ostar, Dir.) (Box 178:, Folder 3127)
  - S. 835 - Ribicoff - Tax Credit Bill (Box 178:, Folder 3128)
  - President Johnson's Budget Cut, 1969 Health Research Facilities Construction Program (Box 178:, Folder 3129)
  - Public Law 90-575 (Box 178:, Folder 3130)
  - H.R. 13786 ( George P. Miller), 1968 (Box 178:, Folder 3131)
  - Natural Areas Committee (Box 178:, Folder 3132-3133)
  - Nature Conservancy (Mr. DeSousa) (Box 178:, Folder 3134)
  - National Conference of Christians and Jews, Hartford (Box 178:, Folder 3135)
  - Threatened Cuts in Land-Grant funds, 1966 (Box 178:, Folder 3136-3137)
  - NET show - letters regarding it (Box 178:, Folder 3138)
  - New England Council Award (Box 178:, Folder 3139)
  - N. E. Board of Higher Education (Box 178:, Folder 3140)
  - N. E. Center for Continuing Education (Box 178:, Folder 3141-3142)
  - N. E. Council Award (Box 178:, Folder 3143)
  - N. E. Research Application Center (Box 178:, Folder 3144-3145)
  - N. E. State Universities Press Conference in Boston - Proposed (Box 178:, Folder 3146)
  - N. E. String Quartet - Proposed TV series, 1971-1972 (Box 178:, Folder 3147)
  - New Haven 4-H Program (Hill program) (Box 178:, Folder 3148)
  - New Haven Public School System (Box 178:, Folder 3149)
  - Newspapers
    - The Associated Press - D. C. - Garvin Hodgins (Box 178:, Folder 3150)
    - Boston Herald (Box 178:, Folder 3151)
    - Bridgeport Post (Box 178:, Folder 3152)
    - Hartford Times (Box 178:, Folder 3153)
    - New Haven Register (Box 178:, Folder 3154)
    - Meriden Journal (Box 178:, Folder 3155)
    - New Britain Herald (Box 178:, Folder 3156)
    - New London Day (Box 178:, Folder 3157)
    - New York Times - story on out-of-state quota (Box 178:, Folder 3158)
    - The Stamford Advocate (Box 178:, Folder 3159)
    - Wall Street Journal (Box 178:, Folder 3160)
    - Waterbury Republican-American (Box 178:, Folder 3161)
    - West Hartford News (Box 178:, Folder 3162)
    - Willimantic Chronicle (Box 178:, Folder 3163)
  - New Hampshire, University of ( W. Arthur Grant) (Box 178:, Folder 3164)
  - Dan Noble - Dean Brown visit (Box 178:, Folder 3165)
  - Nutmeg - President's Statement (Box 178:, Folder 3166)
  - O (Box 178:, Folder 3167)
  - O'Brien, Archbishop - Gift to U of C on his 25th Anniversary, 1965 May (Box 178:, Folder 3168)
  - Organization for Tropical Studies (Box 178:, Folder 3169)
  - Maynard, Bernadette, Organization of Women Legislators (OWLs) (Box 178:, Folder 3170)
  - Overseas Press Club Foundation (Box 178:, Folder 3171)
  - P (Box 178:, Folder 3172)
  - Prize, Newcomb - Cleveland (Box 178:, Folder 3173)
  - Pardee, Catherine E., Memorial Award Fund (Box 178:, Folder 3174)
  - Parents, UConn, Newsletter (Box 178:, Folder 3175)
  - Dr. Patricio incident, 1970 November 16 (Box 178:, Folder 3176)
  - PEP Board, 1965 December (Box 178:, Folder 3177)
  - Phi Sigma Delta - Celebrity letters (Box 178:, Folder 3178)
  - Pharmacy, School of (Box 178:, Folder 3179)
  - Poellein, John - Elizabethan Singers, 1971 (Box 178:, Folder 3180)
  - Poor Peoples Federation (Box 178:, Folder 3181)
  - Pornography Study, 1970 (Box 178:, Folder 3182)
  - President's Garden (Box 178:, Folder 3183)
  - Putzel, Max (Assistant Dean, Graduate School) (Box 178:, Folder 3184)
  - R (Box 178:, Folder 3185)
  - Radio & TV Center (Box 179:, Folder 3186-3188)
  - Radio & TV Advisory Meeting (Box 179:, Folder 3189)
  - Radio & TV - Don Nelson
    - On the Agenda Shows (Box 179:, Folder 3190)
    - The Courage and the Grace (Box 179:, Folder 3191)
    - Closed Circuit Television (Box 179:, Folder 3192)
    - June 8 - Trip to Amherst (WFCR) (Box 179:, Folder 3193)
    - WELI - Covenant Insurance Co. (Box 179:, Folder 3194)
    - WFCR (Box 179:, Folder 3195)
    - WGBH Proposed show on New England universities (Box 179:, Folder 3196)
    - Channel 18 - WHCT (Box 179:, Folder 3197)
    - WHUS - Complaints (Box 179:, Folder 3198)
    - WICC - Student Participation (Box 179:, Folder 3199)
    - WILI - Mr. Herbert C. Rice, Manger (Box 179:, Folder 3200)
    - WILI - Special Programs (Box 179:, Folder 3201)
    - WILI - Proposed Sports Network (Box 179:, Folder 3202)
    - WINF (Box 179:, Folder 3203)
    - WTNH (Box 179:, Folder 3204-3205)
    - Larry deBear visit to campus (Box 179:, Folder 3206)
    - WTIC - Tom Eaton (Box 179:, Folder 3207-3209)
    - Connecticut Educational TV, Channel 24 (Box 179:, Folder 3210-3215)
    - Michael Radock (Box 179:, Folder 3216)
    - Ramberg, Dr. Hans - Senator Dodd (Box 179:, Folder 3217)
    - McLeod, Bill, meeting with WSM (Box 179:, Folder 3218)
  - Readers Digest (Box 179:, Folder 3219-3220)
  - Research Park - Uconn (Box 179:, Folder 3221)
  - Rhode Island, University of (Box 179:, Folder 3222)
  - Rohrback, John G. (Box 179:, Folder 3223)
  - Roper, Elizabeth K. (Continuing Education) (Box 179:, Folder 3223)
  - ROTC (Box 179:, Folder 3224)
  - Ruder and Finn - Dr. Parrish (Box 179:, Folder 3225)
  - Schimmelpfeng, R. - Library Archives (Box 179:, Folder 3226)
  - S (Box 179:, Folder 3227)
  - Sculptures - Paola S. Abbate (Box 179:, Folder 3228)
  - Security - Students (Box 179:, Folder 3229)
  - Channel 8 (Box 179:, Folder 3230-3234)
  - WOR - Slater Barkentin, R. Beusse (Box 179:, Folder 3235)
  - WPLR (Box 179:, Folder 3236)
  - Seeber, Leonard (Box 179:, Folder 3237)
  - Semester of the Thirties (Box 179:, Folder 3238-3240)
  - Shuttlebus (Box 179:, Folder 3241)
  - Siberian Dancers (Box 179:, Folder 3242)
  - Slate - Petruff show on HDB (Box 179:, Folder 3243)
  - Slater, James A., Dr. (Box 179:, Folder 3244)
  - Sloane, Eric - for President Babbidge (Box 179:, Folder 3245)
  - Smith, Mrs. Carrett (Box 179:, Folder 3246)
  - Social Work, School of (Dr. Carel B. Germain, Dean) (Box 179:, Folder 3247)
  - Solecki, Roman, Dr. (Mechanical Engineering Department) (Box 179:, Folder 3248)
  - Waterford Site - HDB for Trustees Meeting, 1964 June (Box 180:, Folder 3249)
  - Sheehan, Mrs. Janet ( Norwich Free Academy) (Box 180:, Folder 3250)
  - Shopping Center (Box 180:, Folder 3251)
  - Southeast Branch - Letters Received (Box 180:, Folder 3252)
  - SCRPA, Avery Point - Resolution on need for 4-year college (Box 180:, Folder 3253)
  - U.S. Cost Guard Training Center, Booklets and Maps (Box 180:, Folder 3254)
  - Spiritual life of Students (Box 180:, Folder 3255)
  - Southeastern Connecticut Regional Planning Agency (Box 180:, Folder 3256)
  - Avery Point (Box 180:, Folder 3257-3264)
  - SNET Co., ETV leg to WTIC (Box 180:, Folder 3265)
  - Speakers Bureau Information (Box 180:, Folder 3266)
  - Sports Information Office (Box 180:, Folder 3267)
  - Stamford Branch (Box 180:, Folder 3268-3271)
  - Stamen, Ted - Proposal for a 13-week TV show (Box 180:, Folder 3272)
  - State Grange meeting on campus (Box 180:, Folder 3273)
  - Stewart, Porter (Box 180:, Folder 3274)
  - Student Life Committee (Box 180:, Folder 3275)
  - Student Leaders Meeting - Gulley Hall - Dr. Babbidge (Box 180:, Folder 3276)
  - Student Loan Program (Box 180:, Folder 3277)
  - Strike Day, 1970 May 7 (Box 180:, Folder 3278)
  - Summer Science Programs for High School Students (Box 180:, Folder 3279)
  - Summer Youth Orchestra (Box 180:, Folder 3280)
  - Task Force Committee on the Environmental Studies Program (Box 180:, Folder 3281)
  - Technical Services Act of 1965 - Dean Ratchford (Box 180:, Folder 3282)
  - Theft Ring, UConn (Box 180:, Folder 3283)
  - Thut, Isaak, Jr., Dr. (Box 180:, Folder 3284)
  - Time Magazine, Boston Bureau (Box 180:, Folder 3285)
  - Toole, K. Ross - Article in Hartford Times (Box 180:, Folder 3286)
  - Train ride to UMass, 1968 October 26 (Box 180:, Folder 3287)
  - Trees (planted by classes) (Box 180:, Folder 3288)
  - Torrington Branch (Box 180:, Folder 3289-3291)
  - Trueheart, William - Assistant Director of Admissions (Box 180:, Folder 3292)
  - Trustees (Box 180:, Folder 3293)
  - Tuition (Box 180:, Folder 3294)
  - Inter-Tutorial Council (Box 180:, Folder 3295)
  - UAW-AFL-CIO Tax correspondence ( Merlin D. Bishop) (Box 180:, Folder 3296)
  - University of the Air (Box 180:, Folder 3297)
  - University Foundation (Box 180:, Folder 3298-3302)
  - Golf Course - Information from Rutgers (Box 180:, Folder 3303)
  - University Golf Courses Committee (Box 180:, Folder 3304)
  - University Senate (Box 180:, Folder 3305)
  - U.S. News and World Report (Box 180:, Folder 3306)
  - Urban Semester (Box 180:, Folder 3307)
  - Voice of America (Semih Ustun) (Box 180:, Folder 3308)
  - Vermont, University of (Box 180:, Folder 3309)
  - Voting for 18-year-olds (Box 180:, Folder 3310)
  - W (Box 180:, Folder 3311)
  - Warehouse - North Hartford (Box 180:, Folder 3312)
  - Waterbury Branch (Box 180:, Folder 3313-3315)
  - Walsh, Mary Lavin (Box 180:, Folder 3316)
  - Waugh Quadrangle - Connecticut Nurserymen's Association (Box 180:, Folder 3317)
  - Report of home and family living program (Box 180:, Folder 3318)
  - Warehouse - Panthers meeting (Box 181:, Folder 3319)
  - Warehouse ( John Banks) (Box 181:, Folder 3320)
  - Everywhere School (Box 181:, Folder 3321)
  - Wilson, John - SAND (Box 181:, Folder 3322)
  - SAND (South Arsenal Neighborhood Development) (Box 181:, Folder 3323-3331)
  - Noah Webster Application, 1970 (Box 181:, Folder 3332)
  - Wedberg, Stanley, Dr. (Box 181:, Folder 3333)
  - White House Fellows, 1967 (Box 181:, Folder 3334)
  - Whitney, Edwina (Box 181:, Folder 3335)
  - Whittenberg, Charles (Box 181:, Folder 3336)
  - Whitham, George - Proposed Connecticut Radio Garden Show (Box 181:, Folder 3337)
  - Windham Area Community Action Program ( William Olds, Ex. director) (Box 181:, Folder 3338)
  - Woestendiek, W. J. (Editor, This Week Magazine) (Box 181:, Folder 3339)
  - Women's League Day Care Center ( William Vanderdoes, Exec. Director) (Box 181:, Folder 3340)
  - Women Leaders Conference - Follow-up, 1964 June 22 (Box 181:, Folder 3341)
  - Woodhouse, Chase G. (Box 181:, Folder 3342)
  - Women, College discrimination in their selection procedures against, 1965 (Box 181:, Folder 3343)
  - Yankee Conference (Box 181:, Folder 3344)
  - Yankee Factbook (Box 181:, Folder 3345)
  - Yankee Magazine (Box 181:, Folder 3346)
  - Yankee Peers Annual Meeting (Box 181:, Folder 3347)
  - Young Conservatives and John Lupton complaint, 1965 October (Box 181:, Folder 3348)
  - Young President's Foundation (Box 181:, Folder 3349)
  - Loeb Awards, 1973 (Box 181:, Folder 3350-3354)
  - Loeb Awards, 1972 (Box 181:, Folder 3355-3360)
  - Loeb Awards, 1972 (Box 182:, Folder 3361-3374)
  - Loeb Awards, 1971 (Box 182:, Folder 3375-3387)
  - Loeb Awards, 1970 (Box 182:, Folder 3388-3400)
  - Loeb Awards, 1969 (Box 182:, Folder 3401-3408)
  - Loeb Awards, 1968 (Box 182:, Folder 3409-3416)
  - Loeb Awards, 1967 (Box 182:, Folder 3417-3433)
  - Loeb Awards, 1966 (Box 182:, Folder 3434-3442)
  - Loeb Awards, 1966 (Box 183:, Folder 3443-3447)
  - Loeb Awards, 1965 (Box 183:, Folder 3448-3453)
  - Loeb Awards, 1964 (Box 183:, Folder 3454-3457)